<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 10:29:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.15.0.Final released - AWS Lambda SnapStart, new gRPC extension, and a lot more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is our pleasure to announce the release of Quarkus 2.15.0.Final, the last minor release of 2022. As usual, it comes with bugfixes and small enhancements all over the place together with more important changes: Support for AWS Lambda SnapStart Move gRPC extension to new Vert.x gRPC implementation Federation support...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.0.0.Alpha2 released - Second iteration of our Jakarta EE 10 stream</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-alpha2-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We already presented our Quarkus 3 effort here, here and here. Quarkus 3.0.0.Alpha2 is the continuation of this effort. On the Jakarta EE 10 front, it doesn&#8217;t bring anything new, several things are in the works to be integrated in the next Alpha, but it is based on 2.14.3.Final (the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-alpha2-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.14.3.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.14.3.Final with a new round of bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a recommended upgrade for anyone already using 2.14. If you are not already using 2.14, please refer to our migration guide. Full changelog You can get the full changelog of 2.14.3.Final on GitHub. Come...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus support for AWS Lambda SnapStart</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-support-for-aws-lambda-snapstart/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus support for AWS Lambda SnapStart Amazon Web Services (AWS) announced the SnapStart feature for AWS Lambda. SnapStart for Java reduces startup latency for Java-based functions running on AWS Lambda, and Quarkus supports it from day one! Quarkus is supersonic subatomic Java with a focus on cloud-native applications. The idea...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-support-for-aws-lambda-snapstart/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Shaaf, Syed (https://twitter.com/syshaaf)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.14.2.Final and 2.13.5.Final released - Fix for CVE-2022-4116</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we are announcing the release of Quarkus 2.14.2.Final and Quarkus 2.13.5.Final. Both releases fix CVE-2022-4116 which has been rated as severity high. This fix also hardens CORS handling, including changing 200 OK to 403 FORBIDDEN when a CORS request is rejected because of an invalid origin. It is highly...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Reactive CRUD Performance: A Case Study</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/reactive-crud-performance-case-study/
            </link>
            <description>
                We were approached for comment about the relative performance of Quarkus for a reactive CRUD workload. This is a good case study into performance test design and some of the considerations required and hurdles that need to be overcome. What methodology can we derive for ensuring that the test we...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/reactive-crud-performance-case-study/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>John O'Hara (https://twitter.com/JohnnyDoItAll)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ 1.14.0 released!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.14.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                We are very pleased to announce the 1.14.0 release of Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ. This release adds support for CodeActions and Quick Fixes. CodeActions / Quick Fixes When an error is detected on one of your Quarkus project files, it is highlighted in the source editor (for instance when you...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.14.0/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Jeff Maury (https://twitter.com/jeffmaury)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Redis Job Queue - Reloaded</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/redis-job-queue-reloaded/
            </link>
            <description>
                In How to implement a job queue with Redis, we explained how to implement a job queue mechanism with Redis and the new Redis API from Quarkus. The approach explored in that blog post had a significant flaw: if the execution of a job failed, the request was lost and...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/redis-job-queue-reloaded/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Clement Escoffier (https://twitter.com/clementplop)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.0.0.Alpha1 released - First iteration of our Jakarta EE 10 stream</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-alpha1-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Last week, Max Andersen explained our plans for Quarkus 3 and Jakarta EE 10. I published yesterday a more detailed blog post explaining how we are building the Quarkus 3 stream. It is now time to announce Quarkus 3.0.0.Alpha1 which is the first iteration of our Quarkus 3 stream. A...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-alpha1-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #26 - November</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-26/
            </link>
            <description>
                Yep, you guessed it, it&#8217;s time for the November Quarkus newsletter! Learn about the 2024 Observability roadmap with Roberto Cortez&#8217;s article. Read about making web applications more resilient against certain types of fraud with Erik Costlow&#8217;s "Quarkus Defends REST APIs against Attack" article. Watch a cool video to see how...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-26/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
