<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 12:56:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #17 - February</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-17/
            </link>
            <description>
                The February Newsletter has been published! This month, you can find an introduction to the new Quarkus Superheroes sample application as well as articles teaching you how to get started with Stork Service Discovery, Java Asynchronous Programming with Java, Distributed tracing with Istio, Quarkus and Jaeger, Monitoring Quarkus Prometheus and...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-17/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.7.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-7-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is our pleasure to announce the release of Quarkus 2.7.2.Final, our second maintenance release for our 2.7 release train. Some bugfixes are a bit more involved than what we usually include in maintenance releases, so if you encounter any issue upgrading, please report them with as many details as...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-7-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Superheroes to the Rescue!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-superheroes-to-the-rescue/
            </link>
            <description>
                Are you a developer building microservices? Do you struggle with developing and testing individual microservices that are part of a larger system? Do you want to learn about building REST-based and event-driven applications? Introduction Quarkus has excellent documentation and quickstarts to help developers become familiar with various features in the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-superheroes-to-the-rescue/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Eric Deandrea (https://twitter.com/edeandrea)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Kubernetes Service Discovery and Selection with Stork</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/stork-kubernetes-discovery/
            </link>
            <description>
                As we already described in the previous post, SmallRye Stork is a service discovery and client-side load-balancing framework that brings out-of-the-box integration with Kubernetes, among others. This post will explain this integration, how to configure Stork in a client-side microservice, and how it differs from the classic Kubernetes service discovery...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/stork-kubernetes-discovery/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Aurea Munoz (https://twitter.com/auritamh)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.7.1.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-7-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.7.1.Final, our first maintenance release for our 2.7 release train. It contains bugfixes and documentation improvements, but also a couple of new features, filling a few gaps. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.7. If you are not using 2.7 already, please refer...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-7-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus World Tour 2022 - The Road Never Ends</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkusworldtour-2022/
            </link>
            <description>
                For true rock stars, the road never ends. We’re bringing the band back on the road to continue bringing our unique, hands-on experience with access to Quarkus experts designed to help you get started with Java in a Kubernetes world. Whether you are a Quarkus first-timer or seasoned pro, your...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkusworldtour-2022/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.7.0.Final released - Quarkus CLI maturing, Interactive terminal, Oracle Reactive SQL Client...</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-7-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                2-2-2022 would have been a perfect day to release a 2.2.2.Final version of Quarkus but we didn&#8217;t get that lucky. Today we announce the release of Quarkus 2.7.0.Final. 2.7.0.Final comes with a lot of refinements and new features: Lots of improvements for the Quarkus CLI, that has now been published...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-7-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.6.3.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-6-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We just released Quarkus 2.6.3.Final with a new round of bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.6. Full changelog If you are not using 2.6 already, please refer to the 2.6 migration guide. You can get the full changelog of 2.6.3.Final on GitHub....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-6-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #16 - January</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-16/
            </link>
            <description>
                The January Newsletter has been published! This month, you can find articles about the Java InfoQ Trend report for December 2021, how to use Quarkus with the service binding operator, how to run Qurkus applications on Kubernetes, and lessons learned migrating Spring Boot to Quarkus. Check out Newsletter #16! Want...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-16/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Ask (Quark)us anything!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-insights-qanda3/
            </link>
            <description>
                Time for our semi-annually Q&amp;A session where we drive the episode using your questions! To submit questions comment on this blog or the matching post in our GitHub Discussion forum or post a tweet using the hashtag #quarkusinsights. If an existing question is of interest do upvote questions found in...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-insights-qanda3/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Max Rydahl Andersen (https://twitter.com/maxandersen)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
