<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 03:25:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.9.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-9-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.9.2.Final, our second maintenance release for 2.9. It comes with a bunch of fixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.9 and is highly recommended. If you are not using 2.9 already, please refer to the 2.9 migration guide. Full...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-9-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ 1.11.0 released!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.11.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                We are very pleased to announce the 1.11.0 release of Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ. This release adds support for Qute templates but also align with LSP4MP 0.4.0 and quarkus-ls 0.11.1. Qute templates When a Quarkus project has Qute in the classpath, editing a Qute template (HTML / JSON / YAML...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.11.0/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Jeff Maury (https://twitter.com/jeffmaury)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quinoa - A Quarkus extension to create Modern UI with no hassle</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quinoa-modern-ui-with-no-hassle/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quinoa&#8230;&#8203; To be honest I wasn&#8217;t really a fan at first, but then my wife made them in a bowl like a salad with avocado and raw salmon. Now I really enjoy it with a touch of soy sauce. Let&#8217;s not digress too much, I am not here to talk...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quinoa-modern-ui-with-no-hassle/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Andy Damevin (https://twitter.com/ia3andy)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.9.1.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-9-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is my pleasure to announce the availability of Quarkus 2.9.1.Final, the first maintenance release of our 2.9 release. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.9. If you are not using 2.9 already, please refer to the 2.9 migration guide. Full changelog You can get the full...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-9-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #20 - May</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-20/
            </link>
            <description>
                The May newsletter is out! Read the great article "Native Java in the Real World" describing how Microservices on Kubernetes are the business case sweet spot for native Java because they have the most significant framework and Java runtime overhead. As well as How to use Camel extensions for Quarkus...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-20/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.9.0.Final released - WebAuthn extension, Compression support for Reactive Routes and RESTEasy Reactive and much more...</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-9-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We just released Quarkus 2.9, which comes packed with new features: WebAuthn extension Compression support for Reactive Routes and RESTEasy Reactive Support for Confluent Schema Registry Support for Back channel logout Kotlin and Scala upgrade And much more&#8230;&#8203; Migration Guide To migrate from 2.8, please refer to our migration guide....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-9-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.8.3.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-8-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We just released Quarkus 2.8.3.Final which is the third and probably last maintenance release for our 2.8 release train. 2.9.0.Final will be released next week. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.8. If you are not using 2.8 already, please refer to the 2.8 migration guide. Full...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-8-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Monitoring Quarkus JVM Mode With Cryostat</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/monitoring-quarkus-jvm-mode-with-cryostat/
            </link>
            <description>
                Cryostat is a profiling and monitoring tool that leverages the JDK Flight Recorder (JFR) framework already present in your Java applications running on the HotSpot JVM. Cryostat provides an in-cluster collection hub for easy and secure access to your JDK Flight Recorder data from outside the cluster. Cryostat is a...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/monitoring-quarkus-jvm-mode-with-cryostat/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Andrew Azores</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.8.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-8-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released 2.8.2.Final which, as usual, only contains bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.8. If you are not using 2.8 already, please refer to the 2.8 migration guide. Full changelog You can get the full changelog of 2.8.2.Final on GitHub. Come...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-8-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Solving problems with Quarkus extensions (1/n)</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/solving-problems-with-extensions/
            </link>
            <description>
                This is the first post of what I hope will be a series of several articles showing how you can solve complex problems by leveraging the unique Quarkus build infrastructure and extension framework. First things first, bootstraping a Quarkus extension is easy: in one command, you can get it scaffolded...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/solving-problems-with-extensions/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
