<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 18:03:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code - 1.10.0 release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.10.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code 1.10.0 has been released on the VS Code Marketplace &amp; Open VSX. For a list of all changes, please refer to the changelog. It’s been about 8 months since our last release of Quarkus Tools for VS Code. 8 months!! That&#8217;s a really long...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.10.0/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Roland Grunberg</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #18 - March</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-18/
            </link>
            <description>
                The March newsletter has been sent. Learn about what&#8217;s new with Java 17 and containers, read about LogicDrop and Vaadin&#8217;s path to using Quarkus, and get a look at Continuous testing with Quarkus. Additionally, you&#8217;ll get more insights into how Keycloak is ow fully cloud-native with Quarkus and learn how...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-18/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.7.5.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-7-5-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released 2.7.5.Final which, as usual, only contains bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.7. If you are not using 2.7 already, please refer to the 2.7 migration guide. Full changelog You can get the full changelog of 2.7.5.Final on GitHub. Come...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-7-5-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.7.4.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-7-4-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We just released Quarkus 2.7.4.Final with a new round of bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.7. If you are not using 2.7 already, please refer to the 2.7 migration guide. Full changelog You can get the full changelog of 2.7.4.Final on GitHub....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-7-4-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ 1.10.0 released!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.10.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                We are very pleased to announce the 1.10.0 release of Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ. This release adds support for Quarkus run/debug configurations and provides several fixes (including security fixes). Quarkus configurations It is possible to run or debug a Quarkus application from the IDE configurations. Select the Run &#8594; Edit...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.10.0/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Jeff Maury (https://twitter.com/jeffmaury)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.7.3.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-7-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released a new maintenance release for our 2.7 release train: 2.7.3.Final. Thanks to all the people reporting issues, providing reproducers, fixes&#8230;&#8203;, it&#8217;s really appreciated. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.7. If you are not using 2.7 already, please refer to the 2.7 migration guide....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-7-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #17 - February</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-17/
            </link>
            <description>
                The February Newsletter has been published! This month, you can find an introduction to the new Quarkus Superheroes sample application as well as articles teaching you how to get started with Stork Service Discovery, Java Asynchronous Programming with Java, Distributed tracing with Istio, Quarkus and Jaeger, Monitoring Quarkus Prometheus and...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-17/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.7.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-7-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is our pleasure to announce the release of Quarkus 2.7.2.Final, our second maintenance release for our 2.7 release train. Some bugfixes are a bit more involved than what we usually include in maintenance releases, so if you encounter any issue upgrading, please report them with as many details as...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-7-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Superheroes to the Rescue!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-superheroes-to-the-rescue/
            </link>
            <description>
                Are you a developer building microservices? Do you struggle with developing and testing individual microservices that are part of a larger system? Do you want to learn about building REST-based and event-driven applications? Introduction Quarkus has excellent documentation and quickstarts to help developers become familiar with various features in the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-superheroes-to-the-rescue/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Eric Deandrea (https://twitter.com/edeandrea)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Kubernetes Service Discovery and Selection with Stork</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/stork-kubernetes-discovery/
            </link>
            <description>
                As we already described in the previous post, SmallRye Stork is a service discovery and client-side load-balancing framework that brings out-of-the-box integration with Kubernetes, among others. This post will explain this integration, how to configure Stork in a client-side microservice, and how it differs from the classic Kubernetes service discovery...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/stork-kubernetes-discovery/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Aurea Munoz (https://twitter.com/auritamh)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
