<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 03:03:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.4.3 released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-4-3-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 3.4.3, our second maintenance release for our 3.4 release train (we skipped 3.4.0). It upgrades Netty to 4.1.100.Final, fixing CVE-2023-44487. It also includes a bunch of bugfixes, together with documentation improvements. More releases are planned in the following days/weeks to address the issue in other maintained...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-4-3-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #37 - October</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-37/
            </link>
            <description>
                Read "Integrate your Quarkus application with GPT4All" by Alex Soto Bueno to explore how to integrate GPT4All into a Quarkus application so that you can query this service and return a response without any external resources. Go behind the scenes to learn how to create a CRUD application using virtual...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-37/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>A recap of Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ's latest improvements</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-recap/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ is a free and open source extension, helping users develop Quarkus applications by providing content-assist, validation, run configurations and many other features right from their favourite IDE. This extension is based on the LSP4MP (i.e. MicroProfile) and its Quarkus add-on, and the Qute language server. These...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-recap/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Fred Bricon (https://twitter.com/fbricon)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Processing Kafka records on virtual threads</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/virtual-threads-4/
            </link>
            <description>
                In another blog post, we have seen how you can implement a CRUD application with Quarkus to utilize virtual threads. The virtual threads support in Quarkus is not limited to REST and HTTP. Many other parts support virtual threads, such as gRPC, scheduled tasks, and messaging. In this post, we...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/virtual-threads-4/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Clement Escoffier (https://twitter.com/clementplop)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.4.2 released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-4-2-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 3.4.2, our first maintenance release for our 3.4 release train (we skipped 3.4.0). It includes a bunch of bugfixes, together with documentation improvements. Update To update to Quarkus 3.4.2, we recommend updating to the latest version of the Quarkus CLI and run: quarkus update To migrate...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-4-2-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Testing virtual thread applications</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/virtual-threads-3/
            </link>
            <description>
                In a previous post, we have seen how to implement a CRUD application using virtual threads in Quarkus. The following video shows how to test this application and, specifically, how to detect pinning. The complete code of the application and the tests are available in the virtual threads demos repository....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/virtual-threads-3/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Clement Escoffier (https://twitter.com/clementplop)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Live diff and update quarkus deployments in OpenShift using Jetbrains IDEA</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/live-diff-and-update-using-idea/
            </link>
            <description>
                Prerequisites OpenShift CLI, oc: installation instructions Kubernetes by Red Hat, Kubernetes Plugin for JetBrains IDEA Marketplace Quarkus CLI, Quarkus: Installation Instructions Optional: Source code for this blog post: https://github.com/adietish/openshift-quickstart IntelliJ Kubernetes Plugin This shows you how the Kubernetes Plugin for Jetbrains IDEA is a great companion when deploying quarkus apps...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/live-diff-and-update-using-idea/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Andre Dietisheim</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Writing CRUD applications using virtual threads</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/virtual-threads-2/
            </link>
            <description>
                Last week, we published a video demonstrating the creation of a CRUD application using virtual threads in Quarkus. It&#8217;s as simple as adding the @RunOnVirtualThread annotation on your HTTP resource (or your controller class if you use the Spring compatibility layer). This companion post explains how it works behind the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/virtual-threads-2/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Clement Escoffier (https://twitter.com/clementplop)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Observability in Quarkus 3</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-observability-3-3/
            </link>
            <description>
                Observability in Quarkus Observability on a software system can be described as the capability to allow a human to ask and answer questions. To enable developers and support engineers in understanding how their applications behave, Quarkus 3.3 includes many improvements to its main observability related extensions: quarkus-opentelemetry (tracing) quarkus-micrometer (metrics)...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-observability-3-3/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Bruno Baptista</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.4.1 released - Redis 7.2 and Flyway changes</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-4-1-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is our pleasure to announce the release of Quarkus 3.4.1. We skipped 3.4.0 as we needed a fix for CVE-2023-4853 in 3.4 too. Major changes are: Support for Redis 7.2 Adjustments on how to enable/activate Flyway This version also comes with bugfixes, performance improvements and documentation improvements. We currently...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-4-1-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
