<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 07:07:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.2.1.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 3.2.1.Final, the first maintenance release of our 3.2 release train. As usual, it contains bugfixes and documentation improvements. It should be a safe upgrade for anyone already using 3.1, but if you are using OpenAPI and/or Swagger UI, please have look below. If you are not...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #34 - July</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-34/
            </link>
            <description>
                Read "Quarkus 3.2.0.Final released - New security features, @QuarkusComponentTest" by Guillaume Smet" to learn about major changes like; various new security features, the ability to test CDI components with @QuarkusComponentTest and new build time analytics. Kevin Dubois' article "Managing Java containers with Quarkus and Podman Desktop" shows how to build...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-34/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>On the Road to CDI Compatibility</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/on-the-road-to-cdi-compatibility/
            </link>
            <description>
                Ever since the very first days of Quarkus, the days that are now covered by the blissful fog of oblivion and the survivors only talk about them after a few pints of beer, dependency injection container was an integral part of the envisioned framework. And not just any dependency injection...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/on-the-road-to-cdi-compatibility/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Ladislav Thon (https://twitter.com/_Ladicek)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Explore a new way of testing CDI components in Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-component-test/
            </link>
            <description>
                The Quarkus component model is built on top of CDI. However, writing unit tests for beans without a running CDI container is often a tedious work. Without the container services up and running, all the work has to be done manually. First of all, no dependency injection is performed. Furthermore,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-component-test/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Martin Kouba (https://twitter.com/martunek)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Long-Term Support (LTS) for Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/lts-releases/
            </link>
            <description>
                We&#8217;re thrilled to announce the introduction of Long-Term Support (LTS) releases for Quarkus. We aim to strike a balance between our regular high-paced release cycle and the needs of users who require more stability and predictability. LTS releases offer an opportunity for our community to enjoy a version of Quarkus,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/lts-releases/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Max Rydahl Andersen (https://twitter.com/maxandersen)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.2.0.Final released - New security features, @QuarkusComponentTest</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is our pleasure to announce the release of Quarkus 3.2.0.Final. Quarkus 3.2 is the first of the now announced Long Term Support releases of Quarkus. Even if we will maintain 2.16 for a few months still, we encourage all our users to start their migration journey to Quarkus 3....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.16.8.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-8-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                As mentioned in previous blog posts, we encourage all our users to upgrade to Quarkus 3. However we understand the migration can require some time so we will continue to maintain 2.16.x for a while. Today, we released Quarkus 2.16.8.Final, the eighth maintenance release of our 2.16 release train. As...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-8-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.1.3.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-1-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We released Quarkus 3.1.3.Final, the third maintenance release of our 3.1 release train. As usual, it contains bugfixes and documentation improvements. It should be a safe upgrade for anyone already using 3.1. If you are not already using 3.1, please refer to the Quarkus 3.1 migration guide. And if you...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-1-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Native with Podman for Windows</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/podman-for-windows/
            </link>
            <description>
                Developers who use Windows workstations might face the challenge of running Linux-native workflows. One way to achieve this is by using Podman, a container engine that provides a command line capability to run Linux containers. Podman supports running containers both as "rootful" and as "rootless", with the latter being the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/podman-for-windows/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Karm Michal Babacek (https://twitter.com/_karm)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Dev productivity - Quarkus CLI</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-cli/
            </link>
            <description>
                People hardly realize that the Quarkus CLI was available from the first public release of Quarkus back in 2019. It originally only allowed project creation and extension manipulation. The following command shows the list of supported commands: quarkus --help Usage: quarkus &lt;command&gt; [&lt;args&gt;] These are the common quarkus commands used...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-cli/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Ioannis Canellos (https://twitter.com/iocanel)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
