<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 11:55:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Reactive CRUD Performance: A Case Study</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/reactive-crud-performance-case-study/
            </link>
            <description>
                We were approached for comment about the relative performance of Quarkus for a reactive CRUD workload. This is a good case study into performance test design and some of the considerations required and hurdles that need to be overcome. What methodology can we derive for ensuring that the test we...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/reactive-crud-performance-case-study/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>John O'Hara (https://twitter.com/JohnnyDoItAll)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ 1.14.0 released!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.14.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                We are very pleased to announce the 1.14.0 release of Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ. This release adds support for CodeActions and Quick Fixes. CodeActions / Quick Fixes When an error is detected on one of your Quarkus project files, it is highlighted in the source editor (for instance when you...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.14.0/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Jeff Maury (https://twitter.com/jeffmaury)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Redis Job Queue - Reloaded</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/redis-job-queue-reloaded/
            </link>
            <description>
                In How to implement a job queue with Redis, we explained how to implement a job queue mechanism with Redis and the new Redis API from Quarkus. The approach explored in that blog post had a significant flaw: if the execution of a job failed, the request was lost and...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/redis-job-queue-reloaded/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Clement Escoffier (https://twitter.com/clementplop)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.0.0.Alpha1 released - First iteration of our Jakarta EE 10 stream</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-alpha1-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Last week, Max Andersen explained our plans for Quarkus 3 and Jakarta EE 10. I published yesterday a more detailed blog post explaining how we are building the Quarkus 3 stream. It is now time to announce Quarkus 3.0.0.Alpha1 which is the first iteration of our Quarkus 3 stream. A...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-alpha1-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #26 - November</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-26/
            </link>
            <description>
                Yep, you guessed it, it&#8217;s time for the November Quarkus newsletter! Learn about the 2024 Observability roadmap with Roberto Cortez&#8217;s article. Read about making web applications more resilient against certain types of fraud with Erik Costlow&#8217;s "Quarkus Defends REST APIs against Attack" article. Watch a cool video to see how...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-26/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Our (bumpy) road to Jakarta EE 10</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/our-bumpy-road-to-jakarta-ee-10/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus has been relatively silent on the Jakarta EE front until a few weeks ago, compared to some other frameworks who announced early clear plans with timelines. That doesn&#8217;t mean we were not actively preparing the transition and we have been incredibly busy making it a reality. Most of you...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/our-bumpy-road-to-jakarta-ee-10/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.14.1.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.14.1.Final with some bugfixes and documentation improvements on top of our 2.14.0.Final release. It is a recommended upgrade for anyone already using 2.14. If you are not already using 2.14, please refer to our migration guide. GraalVM/Mandrel upgrade We don&#8217;t usually upgrade GraalVM/Mandrel in a micro...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Starting Quarkus 3</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/road-to-quarkus-3/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus 3 will continue the tradition of propelling Java development forward by moving fast and keep bringing a cutting-edge user experience with the latest technologies. We are happy to make a first Quarkus 3 Alpha available for users to try out and extension writers to integrate with so that we...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/road-to-quarkus-3/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Max Rydahl Andersen (https://twitter.com/maxandersen)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.14.0.Final released - Jandex 3, new Redis commands, caching annotations for Infinispan</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.14.0.Final with a lot of new features and small improvements all over the place: Upgrade to Jandex 3 Include quarkus-opentelemetry-exporter-otlp into quarkus-opentelemetry Additional Redis commands RESTEasy Reactive: multipart form improvements Support for caching annotations for Infinispan Improved Kotlin support for Hibernate Reactive with Panache Support embedding...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Observability Roadmap 2023</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-observability-roadmap-2023/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus has come a long way in the observability space. Initial support for Tracing and Metrics came from MicroProfile and their respective implementations, SmallRye OpenTracing and SmallRye Metrics. Because the observability space evolved, these implementations expanded beyond the original specifications, and the Quarkus extensions providing Tracing and Metrics have been...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-observability-roadmap-2023/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Roberto Cortez (https://twitter.com/radcortez)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
