<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 03:08:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #16 - January</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-16/
            </link>
            <description>
                The January Newsletter has been published! This month, you can find articles about the Java InfoQ Trend report for December 2021, how to use Quarkus with the service binding operator, how to run Qurkus applications on Kubernetes, and lessons learned migrating Spring Boot to Quarkus. Check out Newsletter #16! Want...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-16/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Ask (Quark)us anything!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-insights-qanda3/
            </link>
            <description>
                Time for our semi-annually Q&amp;A session where we drive the episode using your questions! To submit questions comment on this blog or the matching post in our GitHub Discussion forum or post a tweet using the hashtag #quarkusinsights. If an existing question is of interest do upvote questions found in...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-insights-qanda3/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Max Rydahl Andersen (https://twitter.com/maxandersen)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Creating a Quarkus extension for AWS CloudWatch</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-aws-cloudwatch_extension/
            </link>
            <description>
                Creating a Quarkus extension for AWS CloudWatch We recently had the situation that we wanted to log our Quarkus application logs to AWS CloudWatch. Basically it takes some time but is not a big deal. Adding a CloudWatch dependency, creating a Log Handler and push the logs to CloudWatch via...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-aws-cloudwatch_extension/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Bennet Schulz (https://twitter.com/bennetelli)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.6.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-6-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We just released Quarkus 2.6.2.Final, our second maintenance release for our 2.6 release train. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.6 and contains small bugfixes, tweaks and documentation improvements. It also brings back a working Kogito stack. Due to some infrastructure problems, the Kogito team wasn&#8217;t able...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-6-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.6.1.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-6-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                2021 has been a tremendous year for Quarkus and today we officially close our 2021 release season with the last maintenance release of the year: 2.6.1.Final is available on Maven Central and ready for consumption! It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.6 and contains dozens of small...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-6-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.6.0.Final released - SmallRye Reactive Messaging 3.13 and Kafka 3, programmatic API for caching, Kotlin 1.6 and a lot more!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-6-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is my great pleasure to announce the release of Quarkus 2.6.0.Final which comes with some nice changes: Some extensions moved to Quarkiverse Hub SmallRye Reactive Messaging 3.13 and Kafka 3 Programmatic API for caching Smaller image for native executables Built-in UPX compression AWT extension Kotlin 1.6 Camel 3.14 Due...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-6-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Compressing native executables with UPX</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/upx/
            </link>
            <description>
                UPX is is an open-source, portable, high-performance executable packer initially created in 1996. It takes an executable as input and produces a compressed executable. Readers from a certain age may have already used UPX a long time ago when programs needed to be compressed to fit on a floppy disk....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/upx/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Clement Escoffier (https://twitter.com/clementplop)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.5.4.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-5-4-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We just released Quarkus 2.5.4.Final, a maintenance release for our 2.5 release train containing bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.5. If you are not using 2.5 already, please refer to the 2.5 migration guide. Main changes Jackson 2.12.6 We upgraded to Jackson...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-5-4-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #15 - December</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-15/
            </link>
            <description>
                The December Newsletter has been published! This month, you can find articles about; testing a Quarkus Kafka application, exploring Java 17 features with Quarkus, Quarkus bean discovery with Jandex indexing, automating Quarkus with Gitlab, boosting throughput with RESTEasy Reactive in Quarkus 2.2, and Azure resources operator with Quarkus. Check out...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-15/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus is not affected by the Log4J Vulnerability</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-and-CVE-2021-4428/
            </link>
            <description>
                As many of you have heard, the Java community has been rocked by a widespread vulnerability in the Apache Log4J 2 logging library. You can find more details about this vulnerability in CVE-2021-44228 Since Quarkus, its extensions, and dependencies do not use the log4j version 2 core library, it is...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-and-CVE-2021-4428/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Max Rydahl Andersen (https://twitter.com/maxandersen)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
