<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 17:50:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.15.3.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.15.3.Final, our third maintenance release for Quarkus 2.15. As usual it comes with bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a recommended upgrade for anyone already using 2.15. If you are not already using 2.15, please refer to our migration guide. Full changelog You can get the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.15.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                The Quarkus team wishes you a happy new year, and with the new year comes a new Quarkus release, 2.15.2.Final. This version contains bugfixes and documentation improvements for our 2.15 release train. It is a recommended upgrade for anyone already using 2.15. If you are not already using 2.15, please...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.15.1.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is the end of the year (again) and here comes our last release of the year, 2.15.1.Final. We had 9 minor releases this year (starting with 2.7 in February) and so many micros. We made tremendous progress on Quarkus itself and the activity in the ecosystem of extensions has...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Stargate selects Quarkus for its V2 implementation</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/stargate-selects-quarkus-for-its-v2-implementation/
            </link>
            <description>
                This article gives a brief overview of Stargate, why it needed to change, and why Quarkus was chosen for its next implementation. See the references section for additional links to more detailed information. What is Stargate? Stargate, created in 2020, is a data API gateway that transforms Apache Cassandra, an...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/stargate-selects-quarkus-for-its-v2-implementation/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Eric Deandrea (https://twitter.com/edeandrea)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #27 - December</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-27/
            </link>
            <description>
                The year is fast coming to a close so it&#8217;s time for the December newsletter! Learn some common inner-loop development cycle challenges and solutions in Eric Deandrea&#8217;s "Kubernetes-native inner loop development with Quarkus" article. Find out Pierre Guimon&#8217;s approach for migrating a substantial Spring boot code base application to Quarkus...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-27/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.15.0.Final released - AWS Lambda SnapStart, new gRPC extension, and a lot more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is our pleasure to announce the release of Quarkus 2.15.0.Final, the last minor release of 2022. As usual, it comes with bugfixes and small enhancements all over the place together with more important changes: Support for AWS Lambda SnapStart Move gRPC extension to new Vert.x gRPC implementation Federation support...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.0.0.Alpha2 released - Second iteration of our Jakarta EE 10 stream</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-alpha2-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We already presented our Quarkus 3 effort here, here and here. Quarkus 3.0.0.Alpha2 is the continuation of this effort. On the Jakarta EE 10 front, it doesn&#8217;t bring anything new, several things are in the works to be integrated in the next Alpha, but it is based on 2.14.3.Final (the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-alpha2-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.14.3.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.14.3.Final with a new round of bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a recommended upgrade for anyone already using 2.14. If you are not already using 2.14, please refer to our migration guide. Full changelog You can get the full changelog of 2.14.3.Final on GitHub. Come...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus support for AWS Lambda SnapStart</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-support-for-aws-lambda-snapstart/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus support for AWS Lambda SnapStart Amazon Web Services (AWS) announced the SnapStart feature for AWS Lambda. SnapStart for Java reduces startup latency for Java-based functions running on AWS Lambda, and Quarkus supports it from day one! Quarkus is supersonic subatomic Java with a focus on cloud-native applications. The idea...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-support-for-aws-lambda-snapstart/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Shaaf, Syed (https://twitter.com/syshaaf)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.14.2.Final and 2.13.5.Final released - Fix for CVE-2022-4116</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we are announcing the release of Quarkus 2.14.2.Final and Quarkus 2.13.5.Final. Both releases fix CVE-2022-4116 which has been rated as severity high. This fix also hardens CORS handling, including changing 200 OK to 403 FORBIDDEN when a CORS request is rejected because of an invalid origin. It is highly...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
