<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 03:03:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.16.7.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-7-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We released Quarkus 2.16.6.Final, the seventh maintenance release of our 2.16 release train. As usual, it contains bugfixes and documentation improvements. It should be a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.16. If you are not already using 2.16, please refer to our migration guide. Full changelog You can get...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-7-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.0.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We released Quarkus 3.0.2.Final, the first maintenance release of our 3.0 release train (as our first public release for 3.0 was 3.0.1.Final). As usual, it contains bugfixes and documentation improvements. It should be a safe upgrade for anyone already using 3.0. If you are not already using 3.0, please refer...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.0, our new major release, is here!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus 3.0 is the result of a lot of work and dedication from the community. Quarkus continues to be an Open Source stack to write Java applications offering unparalleled startup time, memory footprint, and developer experience. The development of Quarkus 3 started last year on March 18, 2022, with the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>New Features for Qute Templating Engine Support in Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code 1.13.0</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.13.0-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code 1.13.0 has been released on the VS Code Marketplace and Open VSX. This release focuses on Qute Templating Engine Support by introducing support for more sections and improving template validation. New Features Notable Qute features included in Quarkus Tools for Visual Studio Code 1.13.0...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/vscode-quarkus-1.13.0-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Jessica He (https://twitter.com/JessicaJjhe)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #31 - April</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-31/
            </link>
            <description>
                It&#8217;s time for the April Newsletter. Read Willem Meints&#8217;s article "Quarkus: Jave revisited!" where shares his experience with Java using Quarkus after a long hiatus. Learn why Sebastian Daschner thinks Quarkus is a great choice for Enterprise Java in his great video. Learn how to deploy a Quarkus application to...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-31/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.0.0.CR2 released</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-cr2-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 3.0.0.CR2, our last step before building the 3.0.0.Final bits. Please try it with your applications, the update is easy in a lot of cases, and report any problem to us by creating a GitHub issue. To upgrade your application to Quarkus 3.0, see the instructions below....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-cr2-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.16.6.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-6-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We released Quarkus 2.16.6.Final, the sixth maintenance release of our 2.16 release train. As usual, it contains bugfixes and documentation improvements. It should be a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.16. If you are not already using 2.16, please refer to our migration guide. Full changelog You can get...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-6-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.0.0.CR1 released</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-cr1-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is our pleasure to announce the availability of Quarkus 3.0.0.CR1. We are working full steam on polishing Quarkus 3.0 so please try it with your applications and report any problem to us by creating a GitHub issue. To upgrade your application to Quarkus 3.0, see the instructions below. Among...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-cr1-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.0.0.Beta1 released</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-beta1-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is our pleasure to announce the availability of Quarkus 3.0.0.Beta1. We plan to release Quarkus 3.0.0.CR1 next week so now is a good time for testing the migration of your applications to Quarkus 3 (see below for more information about upgrading). Among a lot of bugfixes and small enhancements,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-beta1-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.16.5.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-5-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We released Quarkus 2.16.5.Final, the fifth maintenance release of our 2.16 release train. As usual, it contains bugfixes and documentation improvements. It should be a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.16. If you are not already using 2.16, please refer to our migration guide. Full changelog You can get...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-5-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
