<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 16:57:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.16.0.Final released - Redis time series and preloading, support for XDS in gRPC</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today we released Quarkus 2.16.0.Final with several improvements, bugfixes and documentation refinements. Major changes are: Support for time series operations and preloading data in the Redis extension Support for custom exception handling and XDS in the gRPC extension More flexibility for the Cache extension configuration Several security-related improvements focused on...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Native adopts Adaptive GC policy</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/native-adopts-adaptive-gc-policy/
            </link>
            <description>
                Starting with Quarkus 2.13.6.Final, the native runtime garbage collection policy switched in order to provide more consistent and predictable runtime performance. This blog post tells the story of this switch. Sometime in 2022 while carrying out some native runtime performance benchmarking we observed that, in constant load plain text benchmarks,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/native-adopts-adaptive-gc-policy/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Galder Zamarreño (https://twitter.com/galderz)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.0.0.Alpha3 released - Third iteration of our Jakarta EE 10 stream</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-alpha3-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                As you might know by now, we started a Quarkus 3.0 effort last year and we are continuing this effort, which was described here, here, here, and here. Quarkus 3.0.0.Alpha3 is the third iteration of this work. On the Jakarta EE 10 front, it doesn&#8217;t bring anything new, except for...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-alpha3-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #28 - January</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-28/
            </link>
            <description>
                A fresh new year is a perfect time for some fresh new articles in the Quarkus Newsletter. "Fine-grained authorization for Quarkus microservices" by Raffaele Spazzoli is a great article describing a solution we call fine-grained authorization and uses Quarkus to implement Relationship-Based Access Control (ReBAC) in the manner of Google...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-28/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.15.3.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.15.3.Final, our third maintenance release for Quarkus 2.15. As usual it comes with bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a recommended upgrade for anyone already using 2.15. If you are not already using 2.15, please refer to our migration guide. Full changelog You can get the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.15.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                The Quarkus team wishes you a happy new year, and with the new year comes a new Quarkus release, 2.15.2.Final. This version contains bugfixes and documentation improvements for our 2.15 release train. It is a recommended upgrade for anyone already using 2.15. If you are not already using 2.15, please...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.15.1.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is the end of the year (again) and here comes our last release of the year, 2.15.1.Final. We had 9 minor releases this year (starting with 2.7 in February) and so many micros. We made tremendous progress on Quarkus itself and the activity in the ecosystem of extensions has...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Stargate selects Quarkus for its V2 implementation</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/stargate-selects-quarkus-for-its-v2-implementation/
            </link>
            <description>
                This article gives a brief overview of Stargate, why it needed to change, and why Quarkus was chosen for its next implementation. See the references section for additional links to more detailed information. What is Stargate? Stargate, created in 2020, is a data API gateway that transforms Apache Cassandra, an...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/stargate-selects-quarkus-for-its-v2-implementation/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Eric Deandrea (https://twitter.com/edeandrea)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #27 - December</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-27/
            </link>
            <description>
                The year is fast coming to a close so it&#8217;s time for the December newsletter! Learn some common inner-loop development cycle challenges and solutions in Eric Deandrea&#8217;s "Kubernetes-native inner loop development with Quarkus" article. Find out Pierre Guimon&#8217;s approach for migrating a substantial Spring boot code base application to Quarkus...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-27/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.15.0.Final released - AWS Lambda SnapStart, new gRPC extension, and a lot more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is our pleasure to announce the release of Quarkus 2.15.0.Final, the last minor release of 2022. As usual, it comes with bugfixes and small enhancements all over the place together with more important changes: Support for AWS Lambda SnapStart Move gRPC extension to new Vert.x gRPC implementation Federation support...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-15-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
