<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 13:57:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.3.2 released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-3-2-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 3.3.2, our second maintenance release for our 3.3 release train. It includes a bunch of bugfixes, together with documentation improvements. The startup performance/memory regression introduced in 3.3 mentioned in the 3.3.1 announcement should be fixed in this version. Update To update to Quarkus 3.3.2, we recommend...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-3-2-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.3.1 released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-3-1-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We released Quarkus 3.3.1, our first maintenance release for our 3.3 release train. It includes a bunch of bugfixes, together with documentation improvements. We are aware of a startup performance/memory regression introduced in 3.3 and are working hard on fixing it. This issue is not solved in 3.3.1 but should...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-3-1-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.2.5.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-5-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 3.2.5.Final, the fifth maintenance release of our 3.2 release train. It should be a safe upgrade for anyone already using 3.2. If you are not already using 3.2, please refer to the Quarkus 3.2 migration guide. And if you are not already using 3.0, please refer...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-5-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.16.10.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-10-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                As mentioned in previous blog posts, we encourage all our community users to upgrade to Quarkus 3. Most of the heavy lifting can be done with quarkus update but be aware that some components were updated to new major versions and that migrating might require some time and careful testing...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-10-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.3.0 released - OpenTelemetry improvements, Reactive Messaging Pulsar extension</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-3-0-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is our pleasure to announce the release of Quarkus 3.3.0. The first thing you will notice in this release is that we dropped the .Final suffix. This suffix was introduced to make sure final releases were sorted properly compared to alphas, beta and candidate releases, at a time where...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-3-0-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #35 - August</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-35/
            </link>
            <description>
                Read Ladislav Thon&#8217;s article "On the Road to CDI Compatibility" to learn about the long road to make Quarkus compatible with CDI Lite. An Elsevier software engineer (Neil Stevens) writes about how to use Quarkus to improve Java functions with AWS Lambda in "Elsevier Tech: Writing a native Java Lambda...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-35/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.2.4.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-4-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 3.2.4.Final, the fourth maintenance release of our 3.2 release train. It should be a safe upgrade for anyone already using 3.2. If you are not already using 3.2, please refer to the Quarkus 3.2 migration guide. And if you are not already using 3.0, please refer...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-4-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.2.3.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                August is upon us but we are still steadily publishing new Quarkus releases. Today, we released Quarkus 3.2.3.Final, the third maintenance release of our 3.2 release train. It should be a safe upgrade for anyone already using 3.2. Note that this version upgrades Hibernate Search to 6.2 as we wanted...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.16.9.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-9-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                As mentioned in previous blog posts, we encourage all our users to upgrade to Quarkus 3 (it is an easy task with quarkus update). However we understand the migration can require some time so we will continue to maintain 2.16.x for a while. Today, we released Quarkus 2.16.9.Final, the ninth...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-9-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Analysing Quarkus Native startup RSS consumption</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/native-startup-rss-troubleshooting/
            </link>
            <description>
                During the development of Quarkus 2.13, we discovered that there was a startup degradation in native mode. One of the key aspects of this degradation was that RSS consumption on start up had gone up by about 10-15% compared to Quarkus 2.7. In this blog post you will learn how...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/native-startup-rss-troubleshooting/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Galder Zamarreño (https://twitter.com/galderz)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
