<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 03:40:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.10.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Summer is here but we keep releasing Quarkus at a steady pace: today, we released Quarkus 2.10.2.Final, the second maintenance release of our 2.10 release train. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.10. If you are not using 2.10 already, please refer to the 2.10 migration guide....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.10.1.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.10.1.Final, the first maintenance release of our 2.10 release train. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.10. If you are not using 2.10 already, please refer to the 2.10 migration guide. Full changelog You can get the full changelog of 2.10.1.Final on GitHub....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Debugging natively compiled Java code with NativeJDB</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/nativejdb-debugger-for-native-images/
            </link>
            <description>
                Co-authored by: Ansu Varghese, Research Software Engineer, IBM In collaboration with: Max Andersen, Dimitris Andreadis, Andrew Dinn, Stuart Douglas, Jason Greene, David Grove, David Lloyd, Thomas Qvarnstrom, Foivos Zakkak, Galder Zamarreno (IBM Research and Red Hat) Quarkus is a cloud-native Java development framework, which allows Java code to be mapped...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/nativejdb-debugger-for-native-images/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Mandana Vaziri (https://twitter.com/mandana_vaziri)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.10.0.Final released - Preliminary work on Loom's virtual threads and various refinements all over the place</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                New month, new Quarkus feature release, you know the drill: Quarkus 2.10.0.Final has landed. This version is a mix of exploratory work and refinements on existing extensions: Preliminary work on Loom&#8217;s virtual threads GraphQL non-blocking support Kubernetes service binding support for Reactive SQL Clients CacheKeyGenerator for cache extension And much...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Using Qute with templates from a database</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/qute-templates-from-db/
            </link>
            <description>
                Introduction I&#8217;m part of a Red Hat team that created a multitenant notifications service which sends the notifications from many Red Hat Hybrid Cloud Console apps (the tenants). Our service can be used to send several kinds of notifications, including emails. Each tenant can create as many email templates as...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/qute-templates-from-db/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Gwenneg Lepage</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #21 - June</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-21/
            </link>
            <description>
                The June newsletter has some great new Quarkus articles. Learn how Banco do Brazil used Quarkus to create a new system to integrate with other financial institutions that participate in the Brazilian Open Banking environment. Get technical on how to configure Podman for Quarkus Dev Services and Testcontainers on Linux...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-21/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Banco do Brasil extracts Open Banking investment data with Quarkus and Kafka</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/banco-do-brasil-open-banking-user-story/
            </link>
            <description>
                Banco do Brasil S.A. is a Brazilian financial services company headquartered in Brasília, Brazil. The oldest bank in Brazil, and among the oldest banks in continuous operation in the world, it was founded by John VI, King of Portugal, in 1808. It is the second largest banking institution in Brazil,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/banco-do-brasil-open-banking-user-story/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Felipe Henrique Gross Windmoller (https://twitter.com/felipewind83)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.9.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-9-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.9.2.Final, our second maintenance release for 2.9. It comes with a bunch of fixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.9 and is highly recommended. If you are not using 2.9 already, please refer to the 2.9 migration guide. Full...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-9-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ 1.11.0 released!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.11.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                We are very pleased to announce the 1.11.0 release of Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ. This release adds support for Qute templates but also align with LSP4MP 0.4.0 and quarkus-ls 0.11.1. Qute templates When a Quarkus project has Qute in the classpath, editing a Qute template (HTML / JSON / YAML...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.11.0/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Jeff Maury (https://twitter.com/jeffmaury)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quinoa - A Quarkus extension to create Modern UI with no hassle</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quinoa-modern-ui-with-no-hassle/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quinoa&#8230;&#8203; To be honest I wasn&#8217;t really a fan at first, but then my wife made them in a bowl like a salad with avocado and raw salmon. Now I really enjoy it with a touch of soy sauce. Let&#8217;s not digress too much, I am not here to talk...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quinoa-modern-ui-with-no-hassle/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Andy Damevin (https://twitter.com/ia3andy)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
