<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 03:36:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.11.1.Final and 2.10.4.Final released - Fixing CVE-2022-2466, new Redis Client API, more customization for some core extensions and more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-11-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released both Quarkus 2.11.1.Final and Quarkus 2.10.4.Final. Quarkus 2.11.1.Final is, despite its name, the first 2.11 release. Both versions are fixing CVE-2022-2466 in the SmallRye GraphQL server extension (for real this time). Unfortunately, the previous fix introduced in 2.10.3.Final and the non-released 2.11.0.Final was incomplete and the issue...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-11-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Ask (Quark)us anything No. 4!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-insights-qanda4/
            </link>
            <description>
                Our fourth semi-annually Q&amp;A session is happening. We meant to do it this week but a case of covid made us take a small break! Instead we will do it on the coming Monday. To submit questions comment on this blog or the matching post in our GitHub Discussion forum...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-insights-qanda4/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Max Rydahl Andersen (https://twitter.com/maxandersen)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.10.3.Final released - Fixes CVE-2022-2466</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                2.10.0.CR1 introduced a major security issue known as CVE-2022-2466 in the SmallRye GraphQL server extension and all the 2.10.x releases are affected (together with 2.11.0.CR1). 2.10.3.Final fixes it and the fix will also be included in the upcoming 2.11.0.Final. You are only affected by this issue if you are exposing...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>How to select the &quot;right&quot; service with Stork?</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/stork-load-balancing/
            </link>
            <description>
                The essence of distributed systems resides in the interaction between services. In modern architectures, you often have multiple instances of your service to share the load or improve the resilience by redundancy. But, when you have all these instances, how do you select the best one? That&#8217;s where Stork helps....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/stork-load-balancing/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Clement Escoffier (https://twitter.com/clementplop)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #22 - July</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-22/
            </link>
            <description>
                The July newsletter is out with some great new Quarkus related technical articles. Learn about "Kafka Streams and Quarkus: Real-Time Processing Events" by Alex Soto and Michael Redlich. Get a better understanding of resilience deisgn patters in the "Resilient microservices with Quarkus and Kotlin - Design Patterns" article by Felicia...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-22/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.10.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Summer is here but we keep releasing Quarkus at a steady pace: today, we released Quarkus 2.10.2.Final, the second maintenance release of our 2.10 release train. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.10. If you are not using 2.10 already, please refer to the 2.10 migration guide....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.10.1.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.10.1.Final, the first maintenance release of our 2.10 release train. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.10. If you are not using 2.10 already, please refer to the 2.10 migration guide. Full changelog You can get the full changelog of 2.10.1.Final on GitHub....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Debugging natively compiled Java code with NativeJDB</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/nativejdb-debugger-for-native-images/
            </link>
            <description>
                Co-authored by: Ansu Varghese, Research Software Engineer, IBM In collaboration with: Max Andersen, Dimitris Andreadis, Andrew Dinn, Stuart Douglas, Jason Greene, David Grove, David Lloyd, Thomas Qvarnstrom, Foivos Zakkak, Galder Zamarreno (IBM Research and Red Hat) Quarkus is a cloud-native Java development framework, which allows Java code to be mapped...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/nativejdb-debugger-for-native-images/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Mandana Vaziri (https://twitter.com/mandana_vaziri)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.10.0.Final released - Preliminary work on Loom's virtual threads and various refinements all over the place</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                New month, new Quarkus feature release, you know the drill: Quarkus 2.10.0.Final has landed. This version is a mix of exploratory work and refinements on existing extensions: Preliminary work on Loom&#8217;s virtual threads GraphQL non-blocking support Kubernetes service binding support for Reactive SQL Clients CacheKeyGenerator for cache extension And much...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Using Qute with templates from a database</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/qute-templates-from-db/
            </link>
            <description>
                Introduction I&#8217;m part of a Red Hat team that created a multitenant notifications service which sends the notifications from many Red Hat Hybrid Cloud Console apps (the tenants). Our service can be used to send several kinds of notifications, including emails. Each tenant can create as many email templates as...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/qute-templates-from-db/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Gwenneg Lepage</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
