<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 03:06:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Website refresh and GitHub Discussions</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/website-and-discussions/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus website got a refresh and we enabled GitHub discussions for community conversations. Website refresh We&#8217;ve refreshed the look&#8217;n&#8217;feel with more contrast on pages for better readability. Cleaned up navigation menu and made a no fuzz "Getting Started" section to show the absolute simplest set of steps to get started...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/website-and-discussions/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Max Rydahl Andersen (https://twitter.com/maxandersen)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Automating Quarkus with GitLab</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/logicdrop-automating-quarkus-with-gitlab/
            </link>
            <description>
                Logicdrop provides a business automation and data intelligence platform that enables enterprises to design their own solutions and run them in the cloud. We process millions of transactions a month across a global client-base and add significant value to mission-critical processes. The Challenge Since moving to Quarkus, our productivity quickly...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/logicdrop-automating-quarkus-with-gitlab/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>KimJohn Quinn (https://twitter.com/logicdrop)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.5.1.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-5-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.5.1.Final, a maintenance release for our 2.5 release train containing bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.5. If you are not using 2.5 already, please refer to the 2.5 migration guide. Full changelog You can get the full changelog...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-5-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Inspecting the Quarkus Native call path universe with Neo4j</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-native-neo4j-call-tree/
            </link>
            <description>
                This blog post is the culmination of an idea that Sanne (Grinovero) floated to me during some lunch, back at a time when we, remote engineers, would occasionally meet face to face and have the opportunity to share ideas spontaneously. I&#8217;m unsure if the lunch was in Neuchâtel or Barcelona,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-native-neo4j-call-tree/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Galder Zamarreño (https://twitter.com/galderz)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.5.0.Final released - GraalVM/Mandrel 21.3 and usability improvements all over the place</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-5-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we announce the availability of Quarkus 2.5.0.Final which comes with the following main improvements: Upgrade to GraalVM/Mandrel 21.3 Support for JPA entity listeners for Hibernate ORM in native mode Ability to add HTTP headers to responses Various usability improvements in extensions and our dev mode/testing infrastructure Migration Guide To...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-5-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>SmallRye Stork meets Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/smallrye-stork-intro/
            </link>
            <description>
                Last week, the Quarkus Insights spotlighted a new project called SmallRye Stork and its integration in Quarkus. In this blog post, we&#8217;re going to give you a concise introduction to Stork. What&#8217;s the problem? Nowadays, systems we build consist of numerous applications, often called microservices. The system&#8217;s overall behavior emerges...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/smallrye-stork-intro/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Michał Szynkiewicz (https://twitter.com/mszynkiewicz)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.4.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-4-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.4.2.Final, a maintenance release for our 2.4 release train containing bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.4. If you are not using 2.4 already, please refer to the 2.4 migration guide. Full changelog You can get the full changelog...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-4-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #14 - November</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-14/
            </link>
            <description>
                The November Newsletter has been published! This month, you can find articles about integration testing in Quarkus, how to use Quarkus and Google Cloud functions, as well as a piece about test-driven development with Quarkus. Check out Newsletter #14! Want to get newsletters in your inbox? Sign up for the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-14/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.4.1.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-4-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We just released Quarkus 2.4.1.Final, a maintenance release for our 2.4 release train containing bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.4. If you are not using 2.4 already, please refer to the 2.4 migration guide. Full changelog You can get the full changelog...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-4-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.4.0.Final released - Hibernate Reactive 1.0.0, Kafka Streams DevUI, Multi module continuous testing, AWT image resize via new AWT extension and much more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-4-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we release Quarkus 2.4.0.Final which includes a lot of refinements and improvements and some new features: Hibernate Reactive 1.0.0.Final Introducing Kafka Streams DevUI Support continuous testing for multi module projects Support AWT image resize via new AWT extension Migration Guide To migrate from 2.3, please refer to our migration...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-4-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Alexey Loubyansky (https://twitter.com/aloubyansky)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
