<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 03:03:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.2.3.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                August is upon us but we are still steadily publishing new Quarkus releases. Today, we released Quarkus 3.2.3.Final, the third maintenance release of our 3.2 release train. It should be a safe upgrade for anyone already using 3.2. Note that this version upgrades Hibernate Search to 6.2 as we wanted...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.16.9.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-9-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                As mentioned in previous blog posts, we encourage all our users to upgrade to Quarkus 3 (it is an easy task with quarkus update). However we understand the migration can require some time so we will continue to maintain 2.16.x for a while. Today, we released Quarkus 2.16.9.Final, the ninth...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-9-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Analysing Quarkus Native startup RSS consumption</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/native-startup-rss-troubleshooting/
            </link>
            <description>
                During the development of Quarkus 2.13, we discovered that there was a startup degradation in native mode. One of the key aspects of this degradation was that RSS consumption on start up had gone up by about 10-15% compared to Quarkus 2.7. In this blog post you will learn how...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/native-startup-rss-troubleshooting/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Galder Zamarreño (https://twitter.com/galderz)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.2.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 3.2.2.Final, the second maintenance release of our 3.2 release train. We released 3.2.1.Final a few days ago but two annoying regressions were spotted before we announced it so we decided to not announce it and release a 3.2.2.Final right away. These two releases contains mostly bugfixes...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Use JFR to profile and monitor native executables</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/profile-and-monitor-native-executables-with-jfr/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus native executables offer many benefits such as even faster start-up time and low footprint. However, one major drawback is that such native binaries can be less observable. The good news is that you can still use JDK Flight Recorder (JFR) when running your Quarkus applications as native executables. Native...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/profile-and-monitor-native-executables-with-jfr/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Robert Toyonaga</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #34 - July</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-34/
            </link>
            <description>
                Read "Quarkus 3.2.0.Final released - New security features, @QuarkusComponentTest" by Guillaume Smet" to learn about major changes like; various new security features, the ability to test CDI components with @QuarkusComponentTest and new build time analytics. Kevin Dubois' article "Managing Java containers with Quarkus and Podman Desktop" shows how to build...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-34/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>On the Road to CDI Compatibility</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/on-the-road-to-cdi-compatibility/
            </link>
            <description>
                Ever since the very first days of Quarkus, the days that are now covered by the blissful fog of oblivion and the survivors only talk about them after a few pints of beer, dependency injection container was an integral part of the envisioned framework. And not just any dependency injection...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/on-the-road-to-cdi-compatibility/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Ladislav Thon (https://twitter.com/_Ladicek)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Explore a new way of testing CDI components in Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-component-test/
            </link>
            <description>
                The Quarkus component model is built on top of CDI. However, writing unit tests for beans without a running CDI container is often a tedious work. Without the container services up and running, all the work has to be done manually. First of all, no dependency injection is performed. Furthermore,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-component-test/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Martin Kouba (https://twitter.com/martunek)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Long-Term Support (LTS) for Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/lts-releases/
            </link>
            <description>
                We&#8217;re thrilled to announce the introduction of Long-Term Support (LTS) releases for Quarkus. We aim to strike a balance between our regular high-paced release cycle and the needs of users who require more stability and predictability. LTS releases offer an opportunity for our community to enjoy a version of Quarkus,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/lts-releases/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Max Rydahl Andersen (https://twitter.com/maxandersen)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.2.0.Final released - New security features, @QuarkusComponentTest</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is our pleasure to announce the release of Quarkus 3.2.0.Final. Quarkus 3.2 is the first of the now announced Long Term Support releases of Quarkus. Even if we will maintain 2.16 for a few months still, we encourage all our users to start their migration journey to Quarkus 3....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-2-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
