<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 03:07:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Kubernetes-Native Development with Quarkus and Eclipse JKube</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/kubernetes-native-development-with-quarkus-and-eclipse-jkube/
            </link>
            <description>
                Table of Contents Introduction What is Eclipse JKube Remote Development? Eclipse JKube Remote Development and Quarkus Wrap-Up This article explains what Eclipse JKube Remote Development is and how can it help developers build Kubernetes-native applications with Quarkus. Introduction As mentioned in my previous article, Kubernetes-native inner loop development with Quarkus,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/kubernetes-native-development-with-quarkus-and-eclipse-jkube/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Eric Deandrea (https://twitter.com/edeandrea)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.16.3.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.16.3.Final, our third maintenance release for the 2.16 release train. As usual, it contains bugfixes and documentation improvements, together with some small enhancements such as the ability to define custom credentials for the Flyway connection. It should be a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.16....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 3.0.0.Alpha4 released - Fourth iteration of our Jakarta EE 10 stream</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-alpha4-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                As you might know by now, we started a Quarkus 3.0 effort last year and we are continuing this effort, which was described here, here, here, and here. Quarkus 3.0.0.Alpha4 is the fourth iteration of this work and it marks a huge milestone: the Jakarta EE 10 stream is now...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-3-0-0-alpha4-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #29 - February</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-29/
            </link>
            <description>
                Read the February newletter to get the latest articles, blogs and insights on Quarkus. Read "Deploy serverless Java apps with Quarkus on Azure Functions" to learn about Quarkus Funqy and its built-in support for the Azure Functions HTTP trigger for Java by Glenn Gailey, Christopher McClister, Daniel Oh, Carolyn McSharry,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-29/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Express Hibernate Queries as Type-Safe Java Streams</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/jpastreamer-extension/
            </link>
            <description>
                Writing Hibernate queries using the Criteria API can be anything but intuitive and comes at the expense of wordiness. In this article, you will learn how the JPAStreamer Quarkus extension facilitates type-safe Hibernate queries without unnecessary complexity. As much as the JPA Criteria builder is expressive, JPA queries are often...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/jpastreamer-extension/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Julia Gustafsson (https://twitter.com/)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.16.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.16.2.Final, our second maintenance release for the 2.16 release train. As usual, it contains bugfixes and documentation improvements. It should be a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.16. If you are not already using 2.16, please refer to our migration guide. Full changelog You can...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>DataCater uses Quarkus to make Data Streaming more accessible</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/datacater-uses-quarkus-to-make-data-streaming-accessible/
            </link>
            <description>
                This article gives a brief overview of the data streaming platform DataCater, discusses how we moved from Scala Play! and Kafka Streams to Quarkus, and presents why we think that Quarkus is an exceptional framework for developing cloud-native Java applications. What is DataCater? DataCater is a real-time, cloud-native data pipeline...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/datacater-uses-quarkus-to-make-data-streaming-accessible/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Stefan Sprenger (https://twitter.com/flipping_bits)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.16.1.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We released Quarkus 2.16.1.Final, our first maintenance release for the 2.16 release train. As usual, it contains bugfixes and documentation improvements. It should be a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.16. For people using Micrometer, the format used to export metrics has changed in 2.16 (for the Prometheus format),...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.16.0.Final released - Redis time series and preloading, support for XDS in gRPC</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today we released Quarkus 2.16.0.Final with several improvements, bugfixes and documentation refinements. Major changes are: Support for time series operations and preloading data in the Redis extension Support for custom exception handling and XDS in the gRPC extension More flexibility for the Cache extension configuration Several security-related improvements focused on...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-16-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Native adopts Adaptive GC policy</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/native-adopts-adaptive-gc-policy/
            </link>
            <description>
                Starting with Quarkus 2.13.6.Final, the native runtime garbage collection policy switched in order to provide more consistent and predictable runtime performance. This blog post tells the story of this switch. Sometime in 2022 while carrying out some native runtime performance benchmarking we observed that, in constant load plain text benchmarks,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/native-adopts-adaptive-gc-policy/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Galder Zamarreño (https://twitter.com/galderz)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
