<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 18:45:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ 1.12.0 released!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.12.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                We are very pleased to announce the 1.12.0 release of Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ. This release improves the Quarkus wizard and Quarkus run experience but also aligns with LSP4MP 0.5.0 and quarkus-ls 0.12.1. Improved Quarkus wizard The Quarkus wizard can be used from File &#8594; New &#8594; Module &#8594; Quarkus....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.12.0/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Jeff Maury (https://twitter.com/jeffmaury)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Hola, 你好, こんにちは Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/l10n-of-quarkusio/
            </link>
            <description>
                Since the launch of Japanese ja.quarkus.io, we got contributors translating the website into (simplified) Chinese at cn.quarkus.io and recently we added Spanish at es.quarkus.io too. These sites are now accessible via the drop-down "globe" menu in the top-right corner. I find it amazing and want to thank the ~30 contributors...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/l10n-of-quarkusio/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Max Rydahl Andersen (https://twitter.com/maxandersen)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.11.3.Final released - Fix for CVE-2022-2466 and other bugfixes</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-11-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                2.11.3.Final is our third maintenance release for the 2.11 release train. It is a safe upgrade for anyone using 2.11. Among other issues, it fixes CVE-2022-2466 that was affected our quarkus-smallrye-graphql extension. Migration Guide If you are not already using 2.11, please refer to our migration guide. Full changelog You...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-11-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #23 - August</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-23/
            </link>
            <description>
                The August Quarkus Newletter has been released! What&#8217;s new this month? Plenty! Get a great understanding of OpenTelemetry with Eric Deandrea&#8217;s article "OpenTelemetry: A Quarkus Superheroes demo of Observability". Get the good and bad experiences of a developer jumping into the deep end on a project with María Arias de...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-23/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.11.2.Final released - CVE-2022-2466 is still ongoing</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-11-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We thought we got to the bottom of CVE-2022-2466, a security issue we have with GraphQL services since 2.10 was released, but this one keeps on giving. This issue is only of importance to you if you are exposing GraphQL services using the quarkus-smallrye-graphql extension. Consuming GraphQL services is fine....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-11-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.11.1.Final and 2.10.4.Final released - Fixing CVE-2022-2466, new Redis Client API, more customization for some core extensions and more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-11-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released both Quarkus 2.11.1.Final and Quarkus 2.10.4.Final. Quarkus 2.11.1.Final is, despite its name, the first 2.11 release. Both versions are fixing CVE-2022-2466 in the SmallRye GraphQL server extension (for real this time). Unfortunately, the previous fix introduced in 2.10.3.Final and the non-released 2.11.0.Final was incomplete and the issue...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-11-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Ask (Quark)us anything No. 4!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-insights-qanda4/
            </link>
            <description>
                Our fourth semi-annually Q&amp;A session is happening. We meant to do it this week but a case of covid made us take a small break! Instead we will do it on the coming Monday. To submit questions comment on this blog or the matching post in our GitHub Discussion forum...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-insights-qanda4/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Max Rydahl Andersen (https://twitter.com/maxandersen)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.10.3.Final released - Fixes CVE-2022-2466</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                2.10.0.CR1 introduced a major security issue known as CVE-2022-2466 in the SmallRye GraphQL server extension and all the 2.10.x releases are affected (together with 2.11.0.CR1). 2.10.3.Final fixes it and the fix will also be included in the upcoming 2.11.0.Final. You are only affected by this issue if you are exposing...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-10-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>How to select the &quot;right&quot; service with Stork?</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/stork-load-balancing/
            </link>
            <description>
                The essence of distributed systems resides in the interaction between services. In modern architectures, you often have multiple instances of your service to share the load or improve the resilience by redundancy. But, when you have all these instances, how do you select the best one? That&#8217;s where Stork helps....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/stork-load-balancing/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Clement Escoffier (https://twitter.com/clementplop)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #22 - July</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-22/
            </link>
            <description>
                The July newsletter is out with some great new Quarkus related technical articles. Learn about "Kafka Streams and Quarkus: Real-Time Processing Events" by Alex Soto and Michael Redlich. Get a better understanding of resilience deisgn patters in the "Resilient microservices with Quarkus and Kotlin - Design Patterns" article by Felicia...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-22/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
