<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 17:40:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.14.1.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.14.1.Final with some bugfixes and documentation improvements on top of our 2.14.0.Final release. It is a recommended upgrade for anyone already using 2.14. If you are not already using 2.14, please refer to our migration guide. GraalVM/Mandrel upgrade We don&#8217;t usually upgrade GraalVM/Mandrel in a micro...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Starting Quarkus 3</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/road-to-quarkus-3/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus 3 will continue the tradition of propelling Java development forward by moving fast and keep bringing a cutting-edge user experience with the latest technologies. We are happy to make a first Quarkus 3 Alpha available for users to try out and extension writers to integrate with so that we...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/road-to-quarkus-3/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Max Rydahl Andersen (https://twitter.com/maxandersen)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.14.0.Final released - Jandex 3, new Redis commands, caching annotations for Infinispan</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.14.0.Final with a lot of new features and small improvements all over the place: Upgrade to Jandex 3 Include quarkus-opentelemetry-exporter-otlp into quarkus-opentelemetry Additional Redis commands RESTEasy Reactive: multipart form improvements Support for caching annotations for Infinispan Improved Kotlin support for Hibernate Reactive with Panache Support embedding...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-14-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Observability Roadmap 2023</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-observability-roadmap-2023/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus has come a long way in the observability space. Initial support for Tracing and Metrics came from MicroProfile and their respective implementations, SmallRye OpenTracing and SmallRye Metrics. Because the observability space evolved, these implementations expanded beyond the original specifications, and the Quarkus extensions providing Tracing and Metrics have been...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-observability-roadmap-2023/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Roberto Cortez (https://twitter.com/radcortez)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.13.4.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-13-4-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.13.4.Final with a new round of bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a recommended upgrade for anyone already using 2.13. If you are not already using 2.13, please refer to our migration guide. GraalVM/Mandrel upgrade We don&#8217;t usually upgrade GraalVM/Mandrel in a micro release but GraalVM/Mandrel...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-13-4-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.13.3.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-13-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.13.3.Final with a new round of bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a recommended and safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.13. Especially since it fixes a Jackson CVE (even if you probably are not affected by the CVE, better be safe). If you are not...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-13-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.13.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-13-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                2.13.2.Final is the second maintenance release of the 2.13 release train. As usual, it contains bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a recommended and safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.13. If you are not already using 2.13, please refer to our migration guide. Full changelog You can get the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-13-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #25 - October</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-25/
            </link>
            <description>
                It&#8217;s that time of the month&#8230;&#8203; time for the latest Quarkus newsletter! "Tutorial: Build a Quarkus web app with Azure App Service on Linux and PostgreSQL" walks you through the process of building, configuring, deploying, and scaling Java web apps on Azure. Vamil Kumar&#8217;s article; "Service discovery using SmallRye Stork...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-25/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.13.1.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-13-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                2.13.1.Final is the first maintenance release of the 2.13 release train. It comes with a bunch of bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a recommended and safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.13. If you are not already using 2.13, please refer to our migration guide. Full changelog You can...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-13-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.13.0.Final released - Cross site request forgery prevention filter, Kafka Dev UI</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-13-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We don&#8217;t have a ton of big new features in Quarkus 2.13.0.Final but it comes with a ton of small enhancements that should improve your overall experience with Quarkus. It still comes with some exciting stuff: Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) prevention filter for RESTEasy Reactive (well, security is not...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-13-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
